<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Python Benin</title>
    <link>https://pythonbenin.com/en/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Python Benin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>fr-FR</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 20:28:42 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pythonbenin.com/en/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Trees by Joyce Kilmer</title>
      <link>https://pythonbenin.com/en/trees-by-joyce-kilmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 20:28:42 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pythonbenin.com/en/trees-by-joyce-kilmer/</guid>
      <description>I think that I shall never see A poem lovely as a tree.
A tree whose hungry mouth is prest Against the earth’s sweet flowing breast;
A tree that looks at God all day, And lifts her leafy arms to pray;
A tree that may in Summer wear A nest of robins in her hair;
Upon whose bosom snow has lain; Who intimately lives with rain.
Poems are made by fools like me, But only God can make a tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That it will never come again by Emily Dickinson</title>
      <link>https://pythonbenin.com/en/that-it-will-never-come-again-by-emily-dickinson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 23:24:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pythonbenin.com/en/that-it-will-never-come-again-by-emily-dickinson/</guid>
      <description>That it will never come again Is what makes life so sweet. Believing what we don’t believe Does not exhilarate.
That if it be, it be at best An ablative estate &amp;ndash; This instigates an appetite Precisely opposite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If by Rudyard Kipling</title>
      <link>https://pythonbenin.com/en/if-by-rudyard-kipling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 22:14:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pythonbenin.com/en/if-by-rudyard-kipling/</guid>
      <description>If you can keep your head when all about you Are losing theirs and blaming it on you, If you can trust yourself when all men doubt you, But make allowance for their doubting too; If you can wait and not be tired by waiting, Or being lied about, don’t deal in lies, Or being hated, don’t give way to hating, And yet don’t look too good, nor talk too wise:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>